# Henry Chan

Quincy, Massachusetts, United States

h951115951115@gmail.com

(781) 692-5154

# Summary

Permanent Resident since 2016. Linux Foundation Certified System Administrator. AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner. Completed most courses at mongoDB University. Learning HTML and JavaScript. Impressed by the concept of SRE proposed by Google. I am building my first webpage: https://tfulanchan.netlify.app/

# **Experience**



## CON/SAP Intern

Deloitte

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021 (2 months)

- Developed ALV reports and Smart Forms with SAP ABAP at the Global Delivery Center in China
- Provided useful insights to the Learning and Development Manager responsible for Interns recruitment



## **Loss Prevention Officer**

Amazon

May 2016 - Sep 2017 (1 year 5 months)

- Responsible for Front-Desk operations in a Amazon Fulfillment Center
- Managed employee badges for +500 employees and visitors
- Managed team members in night shifts occasionally

#### **Education**



#### King AbdulAziz University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Management Information Systems, General 2019 - 2023



#### (B) UMass Boston

Bachelor of Science - BS, Management Information Systems, General 2013 - 2014

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



https://www.credly.com/earner/earned/badge/9641e750-e5ae-4a29-935a-07b0a060a53e



# Amazon Web Services Cloud Practitioner - Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Issued Jul 2021 - Expires Jul 2024

https://www.credly.com/badges/4f7e80c6-f849-4c5b-8629-f1002ae824fd